dealshabibi.com 2016-03-15

# Privacy Policy - DealsHabibi.com | Deals in Dubai | Best Online Shopping Website | Smartphones Deals in Dubai | Tablets Price in UAE | Cameras Price in Dubai, Sharjah, Abu Dhabi, UAE

**Privacy Policy**

DealsHbaibi respects and protects the personal information you are sharing with us to process your orders or queries with us. We use the latest available technologies and methods to keep the data safely. The below mentioned PRIVACY POLICY lets you know on how we collect  and use your personal information like name, contact numbers, address and how you can control our use of the same.

**Personal information we collect and records.**

On a regular visit to our web site, until unless you register with us or subscribe to any news letter, we don’t record any of the customer data.  Normally the data or information that we can collect from you is the name and address that you may share with us during the registration process or the email address for the newsletter  subscription purpose.  However the registration is not necessary to buy a product through dealshabibi.com . But to complete a purchase, the customer has to fill a Billing Address and Shipping Address form to meet the correct delivery requirement of the customer’s purchase.

**_We assure that the Credit Card details are not stored in company database or server, and will be processed through SSL environment._**

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

**When you visit our Website we send you a cookie. Cookies may be used in the following ways:**

  * To enable the personalization features on our Website (which give you the ability to recall recently viewed pages and see information which you have input on line).
  * To compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our Website and to help us improve the structure of our Website. We cannot identify you personally in this way.

**Disabling / Enabling Cookies**

You can accept or decline "cookies" by modifying the setting in your browser. Please note that if you disable "cookies" you may not be able to use all the features of our Website.

**Use and Sharing of personal information.**

The information that you share with us will be used for the regular operation of our e-commerce business such as:-

  * Process your orders.
  * Respond to your enquiries.
  * Handle orders, deliver items and process payments;
  * Communicate with you about orders, products, services and promotional offers.
  * Update our records and maintain any online account you may have with us;
  * Prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our Website.
  * Enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

We will not sell, publish or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by the law of the country.  Since the information are provided by the customer, if you come across any wrong information or an update required regarding your information stores in the system , please contact us immediately via email or phone.

**Account Information Edit / Update / Unsubscribe.**

Being a registered customer with your own password, you will have full access to your registered account in dealshabibi.com and we provide you with the option to edit or update your stored information. Also you can unsubscribe the email news letter by emailing to [info@dealshabibi.com](mailto:info@dealshabibi.com) with a subject as “Unsubscribe”.

**Information collected / shared by Third-party.**

Our website may contain links to other web sites whose information may be different from ours. Please read and confirm those third party privacy policies as we have no control over the information submitted to or collected by them.

Occasionally dealshabibi.com may use third party permission based mailing / marketing services to promote our offers and information. We do not have access to these names and we obtain these lists under the confirmation from the third party supplier that the supplied addressees have consented the third party to provide the data to outside companies. If you wish to get removed from our communication in such a case, you may contact such third party companies or if you wish to make us ware of a wrong information or un-subscription request, you may reach us via email or telephone.

**Revisions to the Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to revise this policy fully or partially time to time. Please review the privacy statement periodically for changes. Unless otherwise stated, our privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you.
